Andrii Abramov

Java Software Engineer

Contacts

Phone: +38 (097) 884 70 64 LinkedIn: https://ua.linkedin.com/in/andrii-abramov

E-mail: abramov.andrii@gmail.com Github: https://github.com/Abrasha Skype ID: abramov.andrii StackOverflow: https://tiny.cc/abramov-so

Personal statement

I am a young and promising software developer. Mostly, I am specialized on JVM-based languages like Java, Groovy, and Scala. I have more than three years of developing back end as well as client Android applications. I am fond of learning something new, domesticating new technologies and expanding horizons of my knowledge.

Core skills

Programming Languages /

Technologies

- Java, Scala, Groovy
- Android
- Python
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Bash
- SQL, HQL
- OOD & Design Patterns

Methodologies

- Agile
- SCRUM
- Kanban
- Waterfall

Frameworks

- Spring, Play Framework
- Hibernate, Slick
- JUnit, Scalatest
- Akka

Application / Web Servers

- Tomcat
- Jetty

RDBMS

- MySQL
- HSQLDB
- SQLite3

Development Tools

- Intellij IDEA
- Android Studio
- Gradle advanced, Maven
- Git, Perforce
- Jenkins, Travis CI, CircleCI
- VirtualBox

Operating Systems

- Linux Mint, Ubuntu
- macOS
- Microsoft Windows

Management tools

- Jira
- Trello
- TestRail

Experience

Software Engineer - Kyiv, Ukraine

(August 2017 – now)

Building from scratch Payment aggregation solution.

Duties

- Developing and maintaining microservices architecture
- Requirements collecting
- Automated test coverage
- Deployment and Continuous Delivery

Software Engineer – Kyiv, Ukraine

(June 2016 - August 2017)

Developing and maintaining a large-scaled Android secure library. Designing automated test architecture.

Duties

- Developing Android Secure SDK
- Analysing and debugging code
- Automated test coverage
- Bug fixing
- Maintaining continuous integration server (Jenkins)

Software Engineer - Kyiv, Ukraine

(March 2016 - June 2016)

Developing a full stack web application for managing zoo. It was a project in the SoftServe IT academy.

Duties:

- Feature implementing
- Developing REST service
- Developing client web interface using modern technologies

Education

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Faculty of Applied Mathematics

Bachelor, Graduating in 2018

Certifications

Oracle Certified Professional, Java SE 8 Programmer (April 2017)
Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8 Programmer (September 2016)